isitetv.com 2019-06-14

# Privacy Policy | iSite

#### 1\. INTRODUCTION

 **Purpose of this privacy policy**  
iSiteTV Limited is committed to protecting the privacy and security of your personal data. This Privacy Notice describes how we and our subsidiaries, affiliates, and related entities (collectively “we,” or “us”) collect and process personal data through your use of this website including any personal data you send to us directly through our website or otherwise.

 **By using our web site (isite.solutions or isitetv.com), you confirm that this policy has been read and understood.  
**

 **Controller**  
We are the controller and responsible for your personal data (collectively referred to as “we”, “us” or “our” in this privacy policy).

 **Contact Details  
** If you have any questions about this privacy notice, including any requests to exercise _your legal rights_ , please contact us using the details set out below.

 **Full name** : iSiteTV Limited, company registration number 05676455.  
 **Postal address** : 8 Tollgate Business Park, Colchester CO3 8AB.  
 **Email:**[gdpr@isitetv.com](mailto:gdpr@isitetv.com)

You can also contact us directly via our website contact page.

You have the right to make a complaint at any time to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO), the UK supervisory authority for data protection issues (www.ico.org.uk). We would, however, appreciate the chance to deal with your concerns before you approach the ICO so please contact us in the first instance.

 **Your duty to inform us of changes**  
It is important that the personal data we hold about you is accurate and current. Please keep us informed if your personal data changes during your relationship with us.

 **The data we collect about you**  
Personal data, or personal information, means any information about an individual from which that person can be identified. It does not include data where the identity has been removed. We may collect, use, store and transfer different kinds of personal data about you which we have grouped together as follows:

 **Identity Data –** includes first name, maiden name, last name, username or similar identifier, title, date of birth and gender.

 **Contact Data** – includes billing address, delivery address, email address and telephone numbers.

 **Financial Data** – includes bank account and payment card details.

 **Transaction Data** – includes details about payments to and from you.

 **Marketing and Communications Data –** includes your preferences in receiving marketing from us.

 **Profile Data –** includes usernames and passwords, purchases or orders made by you, your interests, preferences, feedback and survey responses.

 **Usage Data –** includes information about how you use our website, products and services.

We do not collect any **Special Categories of Personal Data** about you (this includes details about your race or ethnicity, religious or philosophical beliefs, sex life, sexual orientation, political opinions, trade union membership, information about your health and genetic and biometric data).

 **If you fail to provide personal data**  
Where we need to collect personal data by law, or under the terms of a contract we have with you and you fail to provide that data when requested, we may not be able to perform the contract we have or are trying to enter into with you.

 **Third-party links**  
This website may include links to third-party websites. Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow third parties to collect or share data about you. We do not control these third-party websites and are not responsible for their privacy statements.

#### 2\. HOW IS YOUR PERSONAL DATA COLLECTED?

We use different methods to collect data from and about you including through:

  *  **Direct interactions** **.** You may give us your Identity, Contact and Financial Data by filling in forms or by corresponding with us by post, phone, email, through the contact page on our website or otherwise.
  *  **Automated technologies or interactions**. As you interact with our website, we may automatically collect Technical Data about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns. We collect this personal data by using cookies, server logs and other similar technologies.

#### 3\. HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL DATA

We will only use your personal data when the law allows us to. Most commonly, we will use your personal data in the following circumstances:

  * Where we need to perform the contract we are about to enter into or have entered into with you.
  * Where it is necessary for our legitimate interests (or those of a third party) and your interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests.
  * Where we need to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation.

Generally we do not rely on consent as a legal basis for processing your personal data.

 **Purposes for which we will use your personal data**  
We have set out below a description of the ways we plan to use your personal data, and which of the legal basis we rely on to do so and what our legitimate interests are where appropriate.

#### 4\. DISCLOSURES OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA

We will only disclose your personal data to third parties where required by law or to our employees, contractors or designated agents or third-party service providers who require such information to assist us with administering the relationship with you, including third-party service providers who provide services to us or on our behalf. Third-party service providers may include, but not be limited to data storage or hosting providers. These third-party service providers may be located outside of the UK.

We require all our third-party service providers, by written contract, to implement appropriate security measures to protect your personal data consistent with our policies and any data security obligations applicable to us. We do not permit our third-party service providers to process your personal data for their own purposes. We only permit them to process your personal data for specified purposes in accordance with our instructions.

We may also disclose your personal data for the following additional purposes where permitted or required by applicable law:

  * To other members of our group of companies (including outside of your home jurisdiction) for the purposes set out in this Privacy Notice and as necessary to perform our contract with you.
  * As part of our regular reporting activities to other members of our group of companies.
  * To comply with legal obligations or valid legal processes such as search warrants or court orders. When we disclose your personal data to comply with a legal obligation or legal process, we will take reasonable steps to ensure that we only disclose the minimum personal data necessary for the specific purpose and circumstances.
  * To protect our rights and property.
  * During emergency situations or where necessary to protect the safety of persons.
  * Where the personal data is publicly available.
  * If a business transfer or change in ownership occurs and the disclosure is necessary to complete the transaction. In these circumstances, we will limit data sharing to what is absolutely necessary and we will anonymise the data where possible.
  * For additional purposes with your consent where such consent is required by law.

#### 5\. CROSS-BORDER DATA TRANSFERS

Where permitted by applicable law, we may transfer the personal data we collect about you to other jurisdictions that may not be deemed to provide the same level of data protection as our laws do, as necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Notice.

#### 6\. DATA SECURITY

We have put in place appropriate security measures to prevent your personal data from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in an unauthorised way, altered or disclosed. In addition, we limit access to your personal data to those employees, agents, contractors and other third parties who have a business need to know.

We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected personal data breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach where we are legally required to do so.

#### 7\. DATA RETENTION

We will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.

#### 8\. YOUR LEGAL RIGHTS

 **You have the right to:**

 **Request access** to your personal data (commonly known as a “data subject access request”).

 **Request correction** of the personal data that we hold about you.

 **Request erasure** of your personal data. This enables you to ask us to delete or remove personal data where there is no good reason for us continuing to process it.

 **Object to processing** of your personal data where we are relying on a legitimate interest (or those of a third party) and there is something about your particular situation which makes you want to object to processing on this ground as you feel it impacts on your fundamental rights and freedoms. You also have the right to object where we are processing your personal data for direct marketing purposes.

 **Request restriction of processing** of your personal data. This enables you to ask us to suspend the processing of your personal data in the following scenarios: (a) if you want us to establish the data’s accuracy; (b) where our use of the data is unlawful but you do not want us to erase it; (c) where you need us to hold the data even if we no longer require it as you need it to establish, exercise or defend legal claims; or (d) you have objected to our use of your data but we need to verify whether we have overriding legitimate grounds to use it.

 **Request the transfer** of your personal data to you or to a third party. We will provide to you, or a third party you have chosen, your personal data in a structured, commonly used, machine-readable format. Note that this right only applies to automated information which you initially provided consent for us to use or where we used the information to perform a contract with you.

 **Withdraw consent at any time** where we are relying on consent to process your personal data.

 **No fee usually required**. You will not have to pay a fee to access your personal data (or to exercise any of the other rights). However, we may charge a reasonable fee if your request is clearly unfounded, repetitive or excessive. Alternatively, we may refuse to comply with your request in these circumstances.
